Guide to the Bruce T. Wilkins papers,1960-2002.
Wilkins, Bruce T. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Bruce T. Wilkins papers, 1960-2002.
21-18-3240
Bruce T.(Bruce Tabor), Wilkins 1931-
7.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Publications, Reports, Scrapbooks, Research Materials, Diaries
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, memoranda, plans of work, course material and subject files, concerning Bruce Wilkins' career in the Dept. of Natural Resources (formerly the Dept. of Conservation) including material on fisheries and the Sea Grant Program.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor Emeritus of Natural Resources, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, memoranda, plans of work, course material and subject files, concerning Bruce Wilkins' career in the Dept. of Natural Resources (formerly the Dept. of Conservation) including material on fisheries and the Sea Grant Program.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Wilkins, Bruce T.1931-; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University.Natural Resources Dept.; Cornell University.Conservation Dept.; New York Sea Grant Extension Program.
Subjects:
Fisheries.; Conservation of natural resources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- American Fisheries Society 125th Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Fisheries Society Publications Awards Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual Report Dept. of Natural Resources CCE, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bruce T. Wilkins Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bruce T. Wilkins- Leave of absence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bruce T. Wilkins Personal (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bruce T. Wilkins Resume and Publications, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- CCE Natural Resources Staff Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Clara Dickson Hall-MacDickson, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Common Property Issues Ghana Paper, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Conservation 150-Spring Seminar in Integrated Resources Development (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cornell Adult University Overall Plan, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1969-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Costa Rica Trip Correspondence and Email, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Curriculum Committee Activities-Dinners,Lunches,etc., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Department Curriculum Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Curriculum Committee New Courses Correspondence, Memos-Charles Smith, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Curriculum Integrative Group-Memos, Course Descriptions,Syllabi, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- DEC Session, May 1-2 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Department of Natural Resources Teaching and Curriclum Committee Meetings Minutes, 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Department Teaching Faculty Meeting Minutes, Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Environmental Studies Curriculum Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Grey, Gene W. Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- HATCH Act, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Interactive Videodiscs and Wildlife Management, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Inter-Collegiate Outdoor Recreation Group Minutes, Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- International Symposium on Society and Resource Management, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Marine Angler Data- Reports Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Marine Policy, Spring 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Memos to Staff, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Memos, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Narrative Plan of Work and Evaluation Plan, 1975-1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Narratives, January 1980 -June 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Narratives, July 1980- December 1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Narratives Hawaii Correspondence, Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Narratives, July 1982- December 1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Narratives, January 1983 - June 1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Narratives, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Natural Resources and Conservation Services (NRCS) Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Natural Resources Emphases and Accomplishments Reports, Memos, Courses, 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- NE Conference- Memos, Correspondence, May 7-10 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- NRES 107 Final Exam (Box 1, Folder 42)
- NRES 438 Fishery Management Course, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- NRES 494 Conflict Resolution Syllabus, Memos, Coursework, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- NRES 496 Conservation and Sustainable Development (Box 1, Folder 45)
- NRES 604, Fall 1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- NRES 604- Memos, Coursework, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- NRES 604 Memos, Evaluation, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- NRES 606 Marine Resources Policies, Syllabus, Menus,Coursework, 1979-1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- NRES 606 Syllabus, Coursework, Spring 1993 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Oglesby, Ray- Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Other Recreation Research Possibilities Catalogs, Memos, Papers, Correspondence, 1966-1984 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Plan of Work, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Plan of Work, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Resource Analysis and Planning Major (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Resource Policy and Human Studies Group, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Resource Policy and Planning- Committee Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Sea Grant Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Sea Grant Extension Program, 1975-1988 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Teaching Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Teaching - Miscellaneous Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Wildlife Society- Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Agent In Depth M16-20, Memos, Notes, Papers, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Agent Training School, Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Agent Training School, Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Boatman's Conference, April 2, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Charter Boats - Costs and Returns (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cooperative Extension Staff Development, 1973-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cooperative Extension Work Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1963-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cornell University - Department of Conservation- Offerings, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- General - Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1964-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- In Depth Week Course on Fisheries Management, March 21-24 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Legislators' Tour Itinerary, June 29-30 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Magazine Proposal- Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Papers, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Montana Staff, 1958-1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- National Outdoor Recreation Trends Symposium Proceedings- Volume I, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- New York Sea Grant Extension Educational Materials Catalog, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- New York Sea Grant Extension Program Looking Toward 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- New York Sea Grant Extension Situation Statement and Program Plan, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- New York Sea Grant Extension- Situation Statement and Program Plan, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- New York Sea Grant Extension- Situation Statement and Program Plan, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- New York Sea Grant Publications "Alchemy for the 80s" (Box 2, Folder 17)
- New York Sea Grant Publications Annual Report of Program Accomplishments, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- New York Sea Grant Publications- Annual Report of Program Accomplishments, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- New York Sea Grant Publications Cobbler's Cove Slide Set Script (Box 2, Folder 20)
- New York Sea Grant- Publications "Creating the College of the Sea", 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- New York Sea Grant Publications "I Love You, Jay", 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- New York Sea Grant Publications Institute Report, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- New York Sea Grant- Publications Proceedings of the Wetlands Symposium, August 16, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New York Sea Grant Publications "Views on Sea Grant Advisory Service Work", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Sea Grant Extension Program - Resources Notebook, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Sea Grant Extension Program - Resources Notebook, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Nielsen, Larry A.-Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- NRES 620 Course Materials, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- NRES 420 Course Information, Fall 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- NRES and Agr. Econ 350 Course Materials, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Various NRES Courses, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Personal Notebook (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Plan of Work Line Items - Objectives (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Policy and Management Survey, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Profitability Distribution of Camp Grounds Articles and Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Proposals Others, 1967-1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Recreation - Commercial Fishery Conflicts, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Regional Staffing Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Sportsmen Conservation Workshop "Your Organization and Today's Conservation Issues", 1973 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Staff Exchange Program - Sea Grant Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Academic Affairs Faculty Meetings Minutes and Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Alaska Marine Advisory Building, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- British Columbia Land Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Budget Requests, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Civil Service Information, 1948-1952 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Committee Minutes, 1982-1991 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Computers, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Cooperative Extension Correspondence, Memos and Reports, 1968-1985 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Cornell Recreation Activities - Minutes, Notes and Research, 1965-1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Department Meetings- Minutes, Memos and Reports, 1981-1991 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Departmental Positions- Faculty and Staff Descriptions, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Departmental Restructuring Information, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- ECOP Reports, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Evaluation, Plan of Work, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- EZRA Proposal - Waterfowl Videodisc Program, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Faculty in Residence Memos, Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Faculty in Residence Memos, Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Faculty Matters- Memos, Proposals and Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Fire Ecology - Courses, Memos and Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Fishery Management, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Foreign Guests, 1968-1978 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Forestry 593 Course Materials, Fall 1974 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Four Year Plan of work, 1988-1999 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Grad Student Information (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Hatch Projects, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Hawaii Site Visit, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Hudson River Study Photos, Correspondence, Memos and Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Introduction of a Proposal, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Japan Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Mid-Career Leadership Workshop, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Miscellaneous Extension Proposals, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- NRES Graduate School Resources Program, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- NRES Graduate Studies, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- NRES 401 Course Description, Spring 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- NRES 402 Course Description - Natural Resources Policy Planning and Politics Background, January 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Readings on Critical Thinking, February 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Student Teaching (inc, Faculty In Residence-Dickson Hall), 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- New York Sea Grant Program Director's Report, 1974-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- New York Sea Grant Institute Project R/FHD-6, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Old Research, 1971-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Old Research, 1971-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Professional Promotion, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Proposed NRES Courses, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Retired Talks, 1967-1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Retired Talks, 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Sabbatic Leave Request Correspondence, Memos and Reports, 1974-1975,1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Science of Conservation Institute, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- NYS Sea Grant Materials, Memos and Correspondence, 1969-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- National Sea Grant College Program Office Correspondence, Memos and Reports, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Sea Grant Background Memos, Notes and Records, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Sea Grant Correspondence from Bruce Wilkins, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- NYS Statement- Sea Grant Extension Program, 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Sea Grant Extension Memos and Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Sea Grant Correspondence and Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Sea Grant Information, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Sea Grant College Program- Correspondence, Memos, Notes, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Society of Parks and Recreation Educators, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- NRES 406 Stony Brook Course, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- University of South California Visit- Correspondence, Memos, Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Wildlife Society Meetings-National Correspondence, Memos, Articles, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Bruce T. Wilkins- Articles, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Bruce T. Wilkins- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Fellowships and Grants, Requests for Bruce T. Wilkins, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Bruce T. Wilkins - Personal Files, Resumes and Publications (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Director's Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Marine Study, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Memos to Leaders, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Narratives - Department of Extension, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- NRES 101 Orientation in Natural Resources, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- NRES 400-401 Correspondence, Memos and Syllabus, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- NRES 406 Final Exams, Spring 1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- NRES 419 Outdoor Recreation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- NRES 420 A Field Studies in Outdoor Recreation (Box 3, Folder 43)
- NRES 420 Evaluations, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- NRES 420 Projecting Participation, 1966-1971 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- NRES 420 Outdoor Recreation, Fall 1971 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- NRES 510 Evaluation Forms (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Participant Data Development Town of Southold, NY, June 1967 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Plan of Work, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Sea Grant Association Executive Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Sea Grant Extension Correspondence, Memos and Reports, 1979-1989 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Committees - Memos, Reports, Notes, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Committees - Memos, Reports, Notes, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Committees - Memos, Reports, Notes, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Committees - Memos, Reports, Notes, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Cooperative State Research Service (CSRS) Review, 1976-1985 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Cooperative State Research Service (CSRS) Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture and Development, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Cornell Institute for Public Affairs Natural Resources Program W 96 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Department Staff Computer Committee, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Dreyfus Foundation Inc. Photos- Correspondence, Memos, Notes, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Dreyfus Workshop Applicants, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Dreyfus Workshop Activities Arrangements, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ECOP Extension Committee on Organization and Policy Correspondece and Memos, 1983-1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ECOP Background and History, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- ECOP Sea Grant Retreat, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- ECOP Evaluations, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- ECOP Sea Grant Advisory Task Force, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Fish Society NY Chapter, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Human Dimensions in Wildlife Study Group, 1963-1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Human Dimensions RP/P Faculty Positions, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Indo-American Fellowship Program Award Application/Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Isles and Shoals, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Long Range Planning Committee, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Marine Advisory Service Program Proposals, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- MESA NewYork Bight Project- Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous- Names, Participants, Workshops, Programs, etc., 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- National Marine Fisheries Service (NMFS) Sea Grant Meetings, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- New Leaders Workshop, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- New York Sea Grant Institute Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- New Staff Training Program Mid-Atlantic Advisory Service Staff, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- New York Sea Grant Institute- Memos, Propossals, Reports, 1969-1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- New York City- 4H, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- North American Conference Quebec, March 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- North American Wildlife and Natural Resource Conference,Louisville, Kentucky Photos, March 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Program Leaders Workshop, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Proposal- Funding Research, 1968-1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Proposal Reviews, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Riverhead Lab Office, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Sea Grant program New Leaders Workshop- Correspondence,Reports, Notes, Articles, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Shoals Marine Laboratory- Correspondence, Memos, Information, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Shoals Marine Laboratory- Policy Courses NRES 606, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Suffolk Cooperative County Extension, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Time Management, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Trip Reports - Bruce de Young, 1977-1985 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Videodisc Project, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Washington DC Intercession- Notes, Memos and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Dreyfus Workshop (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Sea Grant Talks (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Michael Duttweiller - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Bruce T. Wilkins - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- ECOP Meeting - Extension Committee in Organization and Policy, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- IPA - Intergovernmental Personnel Act, Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, Memos, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- IBM Proposal - Personal System Computer, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Bruce T. Wilkins Miscellaneous Information, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Quarterly Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Department Positions, Correspondence, Reports and Memos, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Mentor to Dan-Decker, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Cornell Cooperative Extension Faculty and Staff Meeting, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Resource Policy and Planning, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- NRES 406 - Course Information, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Research Policy and Planning, Meetings Minutes (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Research Policy and Planning, Meetings Minutes, etc. (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Japan Trip, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Science and Technology Extension Service (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Department of Conservation, Natural Resources, Memos, Reports and Statements, 1965-1971 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Department of Conservation, Early Information, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- NRES 501 - Introduction First Meeting (Box 4, Folder 59)
- NRES 593 - Course Information, Fall 1974 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- James P. Lassoie, Department Chairman- Correspondence, Reports and Memos, 1986-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- New Agent Workshop - Sea Grant Program, 1972-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- "Federal Government Decision Making - Application in Outdoor Recreation" By Mark Reimers, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rationale for Agricultural Land Conservation, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Curriculum Review, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Dwight A. Webster- Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Undergraduate Education- Review, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Forest Service (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NRES 510 / Conservation 510 Course Information, 1969-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NRES 401 (Washington), Fall 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NRES 604 Seminar, Fall 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Management Objectives, 1973-1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Cooperative Stat Research Service, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Research Policy and Planning - Long Term, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Norman Portenoy - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Bruce T. Wilkins - Narratives, Monthly Reports and Trip Reports, 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Land Use Survey, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Southold Recreation Phase, Correspondence, Memos and Reports, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Seminar on Blue-fish Harvests, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Southold Project- Correspondence, Notes, Memos and Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Advisory Service Management Committee on Computers, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Michael Voiland Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Fisherman's Forum, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- NRES 606 Course Information, Spring 1981 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Microcomputer Committee Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Building Committee (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Search Committee, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Department Strategic Plan, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Extension Program- Memos, Minutes, 1950-1999 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Department of Conservation - Early Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Cooperative Unit Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Fisheries (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Advisory Committee Meetings, 1995-1966 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Director's Meetings, Spring 1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Early Extension Staff (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Ghana Research Initiative (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Cornell Adult University, Canada, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Resource Policy and Planning, Faculty - Bob Bailey, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Cornell Cooperative Extension Staff Meetings, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Water Quality Proposal, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Great Lakes Involvement Memos, Reports, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- NRES 419- Course Information, Fall 1976 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- NRES 493- Research Policies and Human Students, Spring 1991 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- NRES 420 Course Information, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- NRES 420 Outdoor Recreation Course Information, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Curriculum and Teaching Committee Minutes, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Cornell Angling Research Program (CARP) Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Staff Meetings, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Colin P. Clark - Professor at Large, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Department Extension Leader (Box 5, Folder 50)
- NRES Mini Week Conference, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Department Extension Leaders - Early Period, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Graduate Students Lists, 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Graduate Fields and School Information, 1964-1980 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- 50th Annual Northeast Fish and Wildlife Conference, May 1-4 1994 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Resource Policy Management and Human Dimensions, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Symposium on Society and Resource Management, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- NRES 604 Course Information, Fall 1988 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- NRES 604, Fall 1990 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- NRES 620 Course Information, Spring 1973 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- NRES 606 Law of the Sea, Spring 1995 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- NRES 606 Graduate Students, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- NRES 606, Spring 1995 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- NRES 107, Spring 1992 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- NRES 402 Trip to Washington D.C., Photos, Spring 1994 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- NRES 401, Fall 1993 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Conservation 420, Fall 1971 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Wildlife Society - New York Chapter- Correspondence, Memos, Meetings and Reports, 1988-1993 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Names and Addresses- Pacific, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Invention Disclosure, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Hewlett Foundation Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Search Committee- Hamilton Position, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- RPT 308 and PUB 308, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 73)